Speaker 1: Hi, I'm a lawyer. Welcome to episode 19 of Law for All. This episode we will cover cease and desist basics. A cease
and desist
Speaker 2: letter is a formal written notice requesting someone stop an activity. The
cease
Speaker 3: part means, hey, stop that, and the desist means don't do that anymore in the future starting now.
Speaker 4: In most cases, the
A
Speaker 4: cease and desist letter is not a court order.
It
Speaker 3: is typically sent by an attorney and identifies the conduct at issue, the legal basis for the claim, and the requested action. For instance, off the top of
my head, if
Speaker 3: a former company
Speaker 1: or corporation that you conducted business with asks you to stop making public insinuations, allegations, or dream interpretations of conspiracies,
Speaker 1: to kill or cover up the killing of an employee. The correct way to ask them to stop would be through a cease and desist letter. Receiving a cease and desist letter does not necessarily establish liability. However, continuing the conduct or double downing, as we lawyers say, would be ill-advised or as you laymen say, I know,
Speaker 5: no. Yeah, no. Disclaimer, this
Speaker 6: is not legal advice. Always seek counsel from personal attorneys. Always blame interns
for bad
Speaker 6: legal moves. Dreams are not admissible in court. Doubling downing may or may not
be a
Speaker 6: real term. I'm not a lawyer. I'm
a former
Speaker 6: bowling shoe salesman now addicted to collecting vintage Victorian dolls. This entire video has been a bath salt induced hallucination, not legal advice. Again, not a real lawyer.